dankcash.com 2011-05-17

# DankCash - Privacy Policy

Welcome to DankCash. This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for DankCash's websites and domains.

Our mission is to build users' trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. Because this website wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices.

**This website will notify you of the following:**

What personally identifiable information of yours is collected from you through the website;  
The organization collecting the information;  
How the information is used;  
With whom the information may be shared;  
What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information;  
The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under DankCash's control; and  
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this policy, you should contact DankCash by email to contact@dankcash.com. If you do not receive acknowledgment of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should then contact DankCash by email to support@dankcash.com.  

**INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE**

Members of the DankCash Network include publishers and advertisers involved in advertising transactions. Member information collected includes personally identifiable information that is necessary to conduct business, such as name, phone number, email address, social security number, and/or tax ID number. Payments made to and from DankCash require the provision of and certain collection of personally identifiable information that may include bank account information and credit card numbers. Phone numbers may be used to contact Members for sales or inventory acquisition purposes. All Member information is collected, modified (as needed) and stored in a password protected environment. This information is used for service, media delivery, contact, billing and accounts payable purposes. We will not sell, share (except as provided for herein), or rent this information to non-DankCash entities and publishers. All Member information collection is explicit, voluntary, and manually entered by the Member.

"Cookies" are files (e.g. flash browser objects or http header) that are stored on your web-enabled client (such as your web browser). There are many misconceptions about Cookies, some of which we will try to address in this policy. Cookies cannot erase your hard drive or otherwise damage your computer and do not tell us an e-mail address or any other PII. DankCash does not and cannot use Cookies or web beacons to retrieve PII from your computer. Cookies are used to improve the experience web users have when they see web advertisements. When a consumer responds to or views an Internet advertisement served by DankCash (such as through third-party Web sites or email solicitation) or visits a DankCash Network site, we send a Cookie and/or gif file to assign an anonymous, unique identifier to the end user's Internet browser. One function of these Cookies is to provide DankCash with information for the purpose of paying third-parties commissions when an Internet user clicks on a link, creates a lead, or makes a purchase on an advertiser's Web site. If the Internet user re-visits the advertiser's site directly, DankCash is able to continue to track the user's activities (excluding PII) on the advertiser's site and reward the third-party Web site that referred the user. We may use Cookies to estimate the total reach of an advertising campaign, as well as frequency of display. This allows advertisers to determine with greater accuracy the composition of the audience they reach. Cookies may also be used to control the delivery of a series of advertisements to a web browser, and to limit the number of times a web browser receives any one advertisement. We also may use Internet browsing and online purchase data associated with an anonymous identifier to develop a predictive statistical user profile of the end user's needs and interests. We reserve the right to retain all ad delivery and reporting data as long as may be reasonably necessary for accounting and audit purposes. Cookies are also used to simplify Member login and to facilitate secure navigation through the password protected areas of the website. Cookies may also be used to optimize and personalize the member's experience and allow DankCash to monitor log ins and site traffic patterns. Members who choose to reject all cookies may have difficulty navigating the password protected areas of the website.

We record the IP address of members at each login, and this information is part of a secure database and is password protected.

**Information Sharing**  
Member information is not shared with any third party outside DankCash, except with your consent or as expressly provided for herein or for that necessary to conduct business, such as clearing a credit card transaction for an advertising campaign purchase or making an ACH direct deposit to pay a Publisher or as required by law. DankCash may provide email address and basic account data to an Advertiser or Publisher or third party to facilitate a potential or continued working relationship between the Advertiser and Publisher or for compliance matters. Once an affiliation is established, Advertiser and Publisher (or their agents or other third parties as designated by a Member) are privy to their respective campaign information and PII, including anonymous Internet user transaction data for Internet users referred by Publisher and any other information that a Member may instruct DankCash to disclose. The security of Member information is crucial to our success in the highly competitive field of online advertising. DankCash may, from time to time, use "gallery" pages to identify Publishers and Advertisers by business identity ONLY. In the event that DankCash is acquired by or merged with a third party entity, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information we have collected from you as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors' rights generally, we may not be able to control how your information is treated, transferred, or used.

**Links**  
This website may contain links to other parties' websites. Please be aware that DankCashis not responsible for the privacy practices of such other websites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our website and to read the privacy policies of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this website.

**Security**  
This website employs industry standard security measures to ensure the security of all data. Any data that is stored on our servers is treated as proprietary and confidential and is not available to the public. We have an internal security policy with respect to the confidentiality of customer and other data, allowing access only to employees, or third parties who have a need to know such information for the purpose of effectively delivering our products and services by means of user login and password requirements. We routinely evaluate our data security practices to identify security threats or opportunities for improvement.

No transmission of data over the Internet is guaranteed to be completely secure. It may be possible for third parties not under the control of DankCash to intercept or access transmissions or private communications unlawfully. While we strive to protect your PII, DankCash cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us. You acknowledge and assume this risk when communicating with a DankCashNetwork company.

**Special Offers**  
Our Member email list is used for administrative and business purposes only or as otherwise requested by the Member. We send all new Members a welcoming email. Special offers and promotions may be made at the website.

**Site and Service Updates**  
We may send Members website and service announcement updates by email. Members are not able to un-subscribe from service announcements because they contain important information about the service. We communicate with Members to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account via email or phone.

**Correcting/Updating Personal Information**  
If a Member's personally identifiable information changes (such as his/her email address), the Member should correct and update his/her information in the DankCash Member area.

**Notification of Changes**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post the changed privacy policy and make it accessible on this site along with the date such privacy policy was last updated so our Members are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

**MISCELLANEOUS**  
YOU UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT ANY DISPUTE OVER PRIVACY IS SUBJECT TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND APPLICABLE TERMS AND CONDITIONS. You also agree that you have provided notice to, and obtained consent from, any third party individuals whose personal data you supply to us with regard to: (a) the purposes for which such third party's personal data has been collected; (b) the intended recipients or categories of recipients of the third party's personal data; (c) which of the third party's data are obligatory and which data, if any, are voluntary; and (d) how the third party can access and, if necessary, rectify the data held about him/her.

**Contacting DankCash**  
If you have any questions about this privacy policy, the practices of this website, or your dealings with this website, please email us at contact@dankcash.com
